pollev.com 2011-01-19

# Poll Everywhere Privacy Policy | Poll Everywhere

By using the polleverywhere.com web site (“Service”), a service of Poll Everywhere, Inc. (“Poll Everywhere”), you are agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Privacy Policy”). 

Poll Everywhere collects the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregated information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if Poll Everywhere is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Poll Everywhere will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

## Information Gathering and Usage

When you register for Poll Everywhere we ask for information such as your name, company name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card. Poll Everywhere uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. When you vote via text message on a Poll Everywhere poll, we receive your mobile phone number in order to enable certain features such as the option to prevent multiple responses. We will not release your mobile phone number or other personally identifying information to the poll owner unless you give us permission to. 

## Public Indexing

By default, the polls you create and their results are indexed by search engines, and searchable by other Poll Everywhere users. You can disable this in your settings.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Poll Everywhere service. 

We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to re-login to your Poll Everywhere Polls after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents. 

## Data Storage

Poll Everywhere uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Poll Everywhere. Although Poll Everywhere owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Poll Everywhere application, you retain all rights to your data. 

## Disclosure

Poll Everywhere may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. 

## Changes

Poll Everywhere may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Poll Everywhere primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to questions@polleverywhere.com
